<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss  version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>T-Alerts</title>
    <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
    <description>Recent MBTA T-Alerts</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <generator>MBTA-realtime http://realtime.mbta.com</generator>
    <webMaster>developer@mbta.com</webMaster>
    <ttl>10</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>73</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>The Church St @ Lexington St (layover) bus stop is temporarily closed due to construction. Beginning Monday, April 14, 2014, the Church Street @ Lexington Street stop is temporarily closed due to construction. Customers should please travel west, turn right at Lexington Street, and travel north to the nearest accessible location on Lexington Street @ Church Street. 09/11/2014 10:26 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="26578" mode="Bus" line="73" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Severe" delayCategory="construction" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2014 02:26:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts26578</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>64</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Bus stop at Western Ave @ Green St (outbound) moved to 17-21 Western Ave. Affected routes:
64-6
 07/30/2014 11:47 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="29444" mode="Bus" line="64" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="" />
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 03:47:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts29444</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>131</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>7am-3pm: Route 131 (inbound) detoured due to construction &amp; bypasses Porter St @Garfield Rd. Connect at Porter St @Orient Ave &amp; Porter St @Norman Rd. Affected direction: Inbound

Affected stops:
Porter St @ Garfield Rd 07/30/2014 11:47 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="30370" mode="Bus" line="131" name="" direction="Inbound" timing="All" delayTime="Severe" delayCategory="construction" />
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 03:47:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts30370</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitchburg/South Acton Line</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Fitchburg Line service suspended between North Station and Fitchburg on Saturdays and Sundays through November 23 due to track improvements. No substitute buses provided. Affected stops:
North Station
Porter Square Station
Belmont
Waverley
Waltham
Brandeis/ Roberts
Kendal Green
Hastings
Silver Hill
Lincoln
Concord
West Concord
South Acton
Littleton / Rte 495
Ayer
Shirley
North Leominster
Fitchburg 09/26/2014 11:19 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="35525" mode="Commuter Rail" line="Fitchburg/South Acton Line" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Severe" delayCategory="track work" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 15:19:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts35525</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Line</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Buses replacing Red Line service between JFK/UMass and Broadway Stations October 4-5 and October 18-19 Due to the Columbia Junction Signal Replacement Project, buses will replace Red Line trains between JFK/UMass and Broadway Stations in both directions from start to end of service during the following weekends: 

- Saturday, October 4, 2014, through Sunday, October 5, 2014
- Saturday, October 18, 2014, through Sunday, October 19, 2014 

Regular Red Line train service will resume at the start of service on Mondays. All shuttle bus stops are accessible for persons with disabilities. 

Shuttling the following stops: 
Broadway Station
Andrew Station
JFK/UMass Station 10/03/2014 07:16 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="38887" mode="Subway" line="Red Line" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Severe" delayCategory="construction" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 11:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts38887</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Line</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Buses replacing Red Line service between Park Street and Kendall/MIT Stations on October 11 from start to end of service. Due to work performed by MassHighway contractors for the Longfellow Bridge Project, buses will replace Red Line trains between Park Street and Kendall/MIT Stations in both directions from start to end of service on Saturday, October 11, 2014. Regular Red Line train service will resume at the start of service on Sunday, October 12, 2014. All shuttle bus stops are accessible for persons with disabilities. 

Shuttling the following stops: 
Kendall/MIT
Charles/MGH
Park Street 10/01/2014 09:59 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="43325" mode="Subway" line="Red Line" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Severe" delayCategory="construction" />
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 13:59:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts43325</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orange Line</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Buses replacing Orange Line service between Sullivan and Oak Grove Stations on October 7, 14, 20, and 27 from approximately 8:45 p.m. through the end of service. Due to the Assembly Station Project, alternate shuttle buses will replace Orange Line trains in both directions from Sullivan to Oak Grove Stations beginning at approximately 8:45 p.m. through the end of service on the following days: 

- Tuesday, October 7, 2014
- Tuesday, October 14, 2014
- Monday, October 20, 2014
- Monday, October 27, 2014

Regular Orange Line trains will resume at the start of service the next day. All shuttle bus stops are accessible for persons with disabilities. 

Shuttling the following stops: 
Oak Grove Station 
Malden Center Station 
Wellington Station 
Assembly Station
Sullivan Station 09/18/2014 01:24 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="44278" mode="Subway" line="Orange Line" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Severe" delayCategory="construction" />
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2014 17:24:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts44278</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title />
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Escalator 504 PORTER SQUARE - Lobby to Mass Ave unavailable due to maintenance  09/24/2014 05:26 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="44910" mode="Access" line="" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="maintenance" />
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2014 09:26:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts44910</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>554</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 554 (outbound) detoured beginning Thursday, September 25, 2014, due to construction on the Beaver Street Culvert. Due to construction on the Beaver Street Culvert (between Waverly Oaks Road and Warren Street), there will be no outbound service on Beaver Street, Warren Street, Belmont Street, or Lexington Street between Waverly Oaks Road and Waverly Square. Inbound service will run normal routing.

Outbound connections for the Route 554 that travels straight on Beaver Street can be made at Beaver Street and Waverly Oaks Road or at Waverly Square.

Connections for the Route 554 (t) OUTBOUND that travels Forest Street to Trapelo Road can be made on Trapelo Road opposite Briarwood Road or at Waverly Square. 10/02/2014 06:16 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="45052" mode="Bus" line="554" name="" direction="Outbound" timing="All" delayTime="Severe" delayCategory="construction" />
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 10:16:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts45052</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30, 34, 34E, 35, 36, 37, 37/38, 38</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Routes 30, 34, 34E, 35, 36, 37, and 38 detoured from 12 p.m. to 4 p.m. on Sunday, October 5, 2014, due to a special event. Due to the West Roxbury 5K Road Race/Roslindale Day Parade on Sunday, October 5, 2014, from 12 p.m. to 4 p.m., Routes 30, 34, 34E, 35, 36, 37 and 38 will be detoured.

Route 30 
There will be no service to Roslindale Square and Washington Street between South Street and Cummins Highway or Cummings Highway between Roslindale Square and Hyde Park Avenue. 
Inbound connections can be made at Cummins Highway and Hyde Park Avenue or Washington and Firth Streets.
Outbound connections can be made at Washington and South Streets or Cummins Highway and American Legion Highway.

Routes 34/34E
There will be no inbound service to Washington Street from Poplar Street to Forest Hills Station. Connect at Washington and Poplar Streets or at Forest Hills. 
There will be no outbound service to Washington Street between Forest Hills and Roslindale Square. Connect at Forest Hills or Washington and Albano Streets.

Routes 35/36
There will be no inbound service to Belgrade Avenue or Roslindale Square. Connect at Belgrade Avenue and West Roxbury Parkway or Forest Hills. 
There will be no outbound service to Roslindale Square, Belgrade Avenue, or Washington Street. Connect at Forest Hills or West Roxbury Parkway and Belgrade Avenue.

Routes 37/38
There will be no inbound service to Belgrade Avenue. Connect at Centre and Park Streets or Centre and Weld Streets. 
There will be no outbound service to Belgrade Avenue or Centre Street between Holy Name and Corey Street. Connect at Centre Street and Buchanan Road or Centre and Corey Streets. 10/02/2014 06:50 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="45591" mode="Bus" line="30, 34, 34E, 35, 36, 37, 37/38, 38" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Severe" delayCategory="special event" />
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 10:50:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts45591</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80, 87, 88, 89, 89/93, 94, 96</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Routes 80, 87, 88, 89, 94, and 96 detoured from 8:45 AM to 10:15 AM on Sat Oct 4 due to special event Somerville Homeless Coalition 
Davis Sq 5K 
Saturday, Oct 4, 2014

 Route 80
IB and OB Connections can be made at Powerhouse Circle and Medford and Main Streets. No service on Broadway between Medford St and Powderhouse Circle. Connections made at Powderhouse and Warner, Broadway and Medford St

Route 87 
IB and OB connections made at Elm and Porter Sq or Beech and Orchard No service to Elm St between Beech and Davis Sq, No service on Holland, Teele Sq or Broadway

Route 88 
IB and OB Connections made at Highland and Cedar. No service to Highland Ave between Cedar and Davis Sq, No Service to Holland Ave, Teele Sq or Broadway

Route 89
IB and OB No service on Broadway between Medford St and Powderhouse Circle. Connections made at Powderhouse and Warner, Broadway and Medford St or Clarendon Hill

Route 94
IB and OB connections at Powderhouse circle. No Service to College Ave between Powderhouse Circle and Davis Sq, Elm St or Davis Sq

Route 96
IB and OB no service to Beech St, Elm St, Davis Sq Station, College Ave between Davis Sq and Boston St, no Service to Boston St between College Ave and Winthrop St.
Inbound connections made at Winthrop and Orchard or Porter Sq Station, Mass Ave
OB Connections made at Porter Sq Station or Winthrop and Chester. 09/30/2014 12:49 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="45592" mode="Bus" line="80, 87, 88, 89, 89/93, 94, 96" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Severe" delayCategory="special event" />
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 04:49:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts45592</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>69</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 69 detoured from 10 a.m. to 5 p.m. on Sunday, October 5, 2014, due to a special event. Due to the East Cambridge Rib Festival on Sunday, October 5, 2014, from 10 a.m. to 5 p.m., there will be no service on Cambridge Street between Fulkerson Street and Sixth Street. 

Inbound connections can be made at Cambridge Street and Cardinal Medeiros Avenue or Cambridge Street and Fifth Street.

Outbound connections can be made at Cambridge Street and Fifth Street or Cambridge Street and Lambert Street. 10/02/2014 06:20 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="45593" mode="Bus" line="69" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Severe" delayCategory="special event" />
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 10:20:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts45593</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title />
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Elevator 909 NORTH STATION - Lobby to Valenti Way is unavailable on Wednesday, October 8, 2014, due to maintenance. If exiting, travel along the Green Line platform to reach the main station lobby. Once there, pass through the fare gates. Turn right to use North Station Elevator 912 (lobby to Causeway Street) located adjacent to the fare gates. Alternatively, continue down the commuter rail hallway to reach North Station Elevator 941 (lobby to commuter rail and Boston Garden). If boarding, travel one-tenth of a mile down Canal or Beverly Streets to the North Station entrances on Causeway Street. 10/01/2014 09:29 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="45819" mode="Access" line="" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="maintenance" />
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 13:29:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts45819</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title />
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Elevator 910 NORTH STATION - Lobby to the inbound Green Line as well as the Forest Hills-bound Orange Line platforms is unavailable on Thursday, October 9, 2014, due to maintenance. If exiting, exit the train to Haymarket Station and return to North Station on an Oak Grove- (Orange Line) or Lechmere-/North Station- (Green Line) bound train. Alternatively, customers may exit at Haymarket, cross New Chardon Street, and travel three-tenths of a mile down Canal Street to North Station at Causeway Street. 10/01/2014 09:49 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="45836" mode="Access" line="" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="maintenance" />
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 13:49:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts45836</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title />
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Elevator 859 TUFTS - Forest Hills-bound platform to the lobby is unavailable from Monday, October 6, 2014,  through Tuesday, October 7, 2014 due to maintenance. A shuttle will be provided between Tufts Medical Center and Back Bay Stations. If exiting, exit the Orange Line at Back Bay and see station personnel or use the call box to request the shuttle. If boarding, see station personnel or use the call box at Tufts Medical Center to request the shuttle. 10/01/2014 12:56 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="45862" mode="Access" line="" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="maintenance" />
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 16:56:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts45862</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title />
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Elevator 933 COMMUNITY COLLEGE - Lobby to the Orange Line platform is unavailable on Friday, October 10, 2014, due to maintenance. A shuttle will operate between Community College and North Station. If exiting, exit the Orange Line at North Station and see station personnel or use the call box to request the shuttle. If boarding, see station personnel or use the call box at Community College to request the shuttle. 10/01/2014 12:57 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="45863" mode="Access" line="" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="maintenance" />
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 16:57:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts45863</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>424, 450, 455, 459</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Routes 424, 450, 455 and 459 detoured due to construction Affected direction: Inbound

Affected stops:
Western Ave @ MBTA Lynn Garage
Western Ave @ opp MBTA Lynn Garage
Connections can be made at 
Western Ave @ Burns St 10/03/2014 07:23 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46202" mode="Bus" line="424, 450, 455, 459" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Severe" delayCategory="construction" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 11:23:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46202</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>459</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 459 experiencing minor delays due to traffic.  10/03/2014 08:24 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46218" mode="Bus" line="459" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 12:24:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46218</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orange Line, Red Line</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Downtown Crossing: Beginning Wednesday, October 8, 2014, the Washington Street entrance will be temporarily closed due to construction. Affected routes:
Orange Line
Red Line (Ashmont branch)
Red Line (Braintree branch) 10/03/2014 08:40 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46221" mode="Subway" line="Orange Line, Red Line" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="construction" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 12:40:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46221</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orange Line, Red Line</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Downtown Crossing: Beginning Saturday, October 4, 2014, the Summer Street entrance will be re-opened for regular service. Affected routes:
Orange Line
Red Line (Ashmont branch)
Red Line (Braintree branch) 10/03/2014 08:56 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46223" mode="Subway" line="Orange Line, Red Line" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 12:56:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46223</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 15 experiencing minor delays due to traffic.  10/03/2014 09:16 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46227" mode="Bus" line="15" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 13:16:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46227</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 9 experiencing minor delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 10:03 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46234" mode="Bus" line="9" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 14:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46234</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 1 experiencing minor delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 10:26 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46240" mode="Bus" line="1" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 14:26:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46240</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SL5, SL4</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Silver Line - SL4 and Silver Line - SL5 experiencing moderate delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 12:12 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46246" mode="Bus" line="SL5, SL4" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Moderate" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 16:12:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46246</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>47</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 47 experiencing moderate delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 11:57 AM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46248" mode="Bus" line="47" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Moderate" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 15:57:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46248</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 8 experiencing moderate delays due to traffic.  10/03/2014 12:20 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46251" mode="Bus" line="8" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Moderate" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 16:20:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46251</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title />
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Elevator 844 GREEN STREET - Orange Line Platform to Lobby unavailable due to maintenance If exiting, exit the Orange Line at Forest Hills and see station personnel or use the call box to request assistance. If boarding, see station personnel or use the call box at Green Street to request assistance. 10/03/2014 12:59 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46253" mode="Access" line="" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="maintenance" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 16:59:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46253</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>66</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 66 experiencing moderate delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 01:27 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46255" mode="Bus" line="66" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Moderate" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 17:27:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46255</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>57</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 57 experiencing moderate delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 02:05 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46256" mode="Bus" line="57" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Moderate" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 18:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46256</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 22 experiencing minor delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 01:29 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46257" mode="Bus" line="22" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 17:29:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46257</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 9 experiencing moderate delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 01:30 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46258" mode="Bus" line="9" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Moderate" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 17:30:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46258</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>134</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 134 experiencing minor delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 01:38 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46259" mode="Bus" line="134" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 17:38:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46259</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>108</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 108 experiencing minor delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 01:38 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46260" mode="Bus" line="108" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 17:38:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46260</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>92</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 92 experiencing minor delays  10/03/2014 01:57 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46262" mode="Bus" line="92" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 17:57:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46262</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>558</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 558 detoured due to construction Affected stops:
River St @ School Ave (outbound)
River St @ Bright St (outbound)
Connections can be made at
River St @  Ripley St (outbound)
River St @ Willow St (inbound) 10/03/2014 02:03 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46263" mode="Bus" line="558" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Severe" delayCategory="construction" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 18:03:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46263</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>504</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 504 experiencing minor delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 02:03 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46264" mode="Bus" line="504" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 18:03:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46264</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>350</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 350 experiencing minor delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 02:04 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46265" mode="Bus" line="350" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 18:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46265</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CT2</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>CT2 experiencing moderate delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 02:05 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46267" mode="Bus" line="CT2" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Moderate" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 18:05:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46267</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>41</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 41 experiencing moderate delays  10/03/2014 02:25 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46268" mode="Bus" line="41" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Severe" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 18:25:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46268</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>558</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 558 experiencing minor delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 02:18 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46269" mode="Bus" line="558" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 18:18:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46269</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>36</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 36 experiencing moderate delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 02:26 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46270" mode="Bus" line="36" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Moderate" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 18:26:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46270</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>70, 70A</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Routes 70 and 70A experiencing minor delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 02:33 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46271" mode="Bus" line="70, 70A" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 18:33:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46271</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>137</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Route 137 experiencing minor delays due to traffic  10/03/2014 02:34 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46272" mode="Bus" line="137" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="traffic" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 18:34:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46272</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Line</title>
      <link>http://www.mbta.com/rider_tools/transit_updates/</link>
      <description>Blue Line experiencing minor delays due to a disabled train at Bowdoin  10/03/2014 02:34 PM</description>
      <metadata messageid="46273" mode="Subway" line="Blue Line" name="" direction="Both Directions" timing="All" delayTime="Minor" delayCategory="disabled train" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 18:34:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">talerts46273</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>